It's coming, it's coming, it's coming.
For the first time.
Wooo
Woo-hoo
Woo-oh!
Mr. Usaki caught it
Even if I push it
Wow!
That's great. I don't like it.
I got it!
It's moving.
Oh, my God.
Here it comes.
Almost there.
Whoa!
Where is it?
Ta-da!
He's so cute.
Ta-da! So cute!
Oh, he's swimming.
Wow!
So stylish!
He's not coming.
They're not coming...
I wonder if there will be this many cherry blossoms...
If they don't come, I'll eat them too soon!
Oh, no!
We did it!
Yay!
Delicious!
But they usually eat small fish.
Small fish?
Yeah, they eat small fish.
So that means we're going to use
That's what we're going to use as bait.
Alive.
We're gonna use live bait.
Wow.
Horse mackerel like this
We use these as bait.
Okay, then.
Horse mackerel.
Horse mackerel
Horse mackerel!
Don't go.
Okay, let's see who goes first.
Okay, well, the first person to put in the fish has the best chance of catching it, so...
Okay, then.
Let's go for it.
Let's go.
Go?
I can't go.
Blue and white.
Horse mackerels get into trouble in the water.
If they run this way without permission...
What's that?
If they run toward us, they might get tangled up in the water.
There's a chance...
I wonder if they'll come.
Wrap it up, wrap it up, wrap it up, wrap it up.
Stand up, stand up.
It's out, it's out, it's out. It's not out.
Here it comes!
Stand up slowly.
Hang in there, baby!
That's it!
Wait!
I can't lose!
You don't have to lose.
Just fight it for a while... and let the fish weaken.
Come on!
Like this.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
It's cool.
Slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly.
Slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly.
I can see it.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Almost there.
I'll just come back later.
I see you, I see you.
Come on, Ai!
Come on, just a little bit more.
Come on!
Slowly.
No, no, no...
Wow.
Here we go.
It's big.
It's huge!
The fish are eating it!
Oh, my gosh!
That's amazing.
I got it!
That's great!
I caught it.
I was so worried when I didn't catch it.
I'm so glad we caught it.
Oh! Oh! Stand up at once!
I'm going to put it in your belly!
I'm gonna get it in my belly!
Oh! Here it comes!
I'm here, I'm here!
Oh, my gosh!
Laughing.
LOL!
LOL!!!
Got 2 stews!
Oh no!
Oh! Fish!
Fish!
Fish! Fish!
I got fish!
Oh!
Wow!
Wow! Here it comes!
Wait, wait!
Lift it up!
It's stuck!
Laughing.
LOL!
Put it on your belly!
Lift it up! Slowly!
Lift it up!
Lift it up! And here, lower it for a second while you move forward!
So, stay in front of me!
The same! The same!
Slowly! Um, don't make a sudden decision!
Aah! Oh, no! Oh! Oh, no!
Oh!
It's heavy!
I got it!
It's so heavy!
I can't believe I was pulling this.
What? Huh? What?
Can you do it?
Okay!
Wait, he's not here.
Oh, yeah, I got it. I got it.Oh, I did it. I did it.
I'm getting pulled in.
It's like a tug of war.
There's so many of them.
Whoo!
Please, no relation!
I'm scattered!
Oh, I can see you!
I'm so bad!
I don't have any more HP!
Next girl I want to go!
I wanna go! I want to go!
Nami!
Yay!
Oh my god.
I haven't used the continent this first year.
Wow, hello!
You did a great job.
Thanks for all your hard work.
congratulations!
I want to eat.
I wanna eat.
I want to eat!
I got a shimmering margin!
Ta-da!
I'm so used to touching the fish that I can touch it now!
I thought I couldn't touch it at first.
But now it looks so cute!
I caught so many fish!
Yay!
Oh, my gosh! So many fish!
17 fish!
That's great!
That's great! Oh, my gosh!
They're so big!
They look delicious!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
I'm getting too fat.
Is that okay?
OK!
It's done!
Please take a look!
Yes! So, I made sashimi from the fish I caught!
Well, the video looks as if I did all the work.
I only did the last slice, didn't I, Rennpan?
Is that right?
Wow, the teacher ate a lot of food.
Thank you very much!
But the serving size is a mess!
That's amazing!
The way you served it...
Shall we start from the top and say what kind of fish it is?
Shimaji taiwasa!
Let's thank God and eat!
Bon appétit!
How original!
We do this all the time at school!
Delicious!
Yum!
Yeah! Yeah!
Yum! Yum!
It's so good!
I want some white rice!
Yeah!
It's so tangy and spicy, too!
Yeah! And it's so sweet!
Yes! Yes, indeed!
Yes!
The more sweet-sweet you feel!
Hey!
Delicious!
It's nothing but delicious! It's so good!
I'm in! This is it!
Delicious!
This is it!
I'll have some straw!
Bon appétit!
Okay! A little big!
Delicious!
Bon appétit!
Mmm!
Ooh!
Compared to
Compared to my previous fish
The flesh feels thicker!
Yes!
The rest of the fish is a little different too!
Maybe it's because we cut it!
Maybe Peter didn't cut it!
That's right!
Lupin's the only one who cut this one!
Right!
But it's so thick!
It's worth eating!
Look at it before you cut it.
I thought it looked a little fatty!
I thought it looked a little fatty.
But it's delicious!
It also has a delicious aftertaste!
Yes!
But it's also quite filling.
It feels fresh!
Freshly caught!
Celebrate!
Delicious!
The flavor of the fish
You can feel the flavor of the fish even when it's grilled!
The grilled fish is also very tasty!
You can feel the salt well.
When you bite into it, you can feel the taste of the fish.
Delicious!
Very fluffy!
Eat with the color of the tie!
Eat with the color of a Thai!
Eat it with the color of Thailand!
You'll feel Thailand directly!
That's great!
I want to feel it the most!
So, thank you for the food!
Thank you for the food!
It was delicious!
I'm full!
We caught the fish ourselves
And having it cooked for us
It was so great to eat it!
Really!
I felt so satisfied!
So much!
I now know how fun fishing can be.
Once you catch a fish
I'm like, "I'm having fun! I feel like
I want to fish again and again.
Eating fresh fish right away
It was so delicious.
It was fun!
I've seen the drama "Chulu Nandi" and
I can't wait to eat the fish I caught.
the fun of fishing until you eat the fish you catch.
We were able to experience it for the first time
It was the first time for us to experience it for ourselves.
It's really good!
One more time!
I can't wait to see it again!
Drama tutu nandi part 2 will be
If it ever comes.
I'm sure the four of us would fish it perfectly!
We are fishing!
Please wait!Please wait!
Where can we go next?
I'm looking forward to it!
I don't know if we'll be overseas yet.
Enjoy!
So that's all for us VOLTA!
Bye bye!